Congratulations on finishing up this Power BI case study!
The HealthStat team now has a powerful report that really enables an understanding
of the key impacts on average LOS and cost for hospitals across the state of New York.
This benchmarking will inform where targeted quality improvements can be made to
both improve the hospital's operational efficiency as well as the patient experience.
Congratulations on completing the case study.
We've covered many topics across this case study from data modeling,
exploratory data analysis, root cause analysis, DAX calculations and report design.
Be sure to check out the other Power BI case studies available on DataCamp!
Here's a list of some case studies already available for you to check out.
Great work on this Power BI case study.
Congratulations!